Thanks.
Ron.
Worry.
Thank you all right down the.
Stairway Our don't move keep calm don't
get excited I get out of the right way so
you can.
Help. Put it we have
nothing at a blow up I don't
understand it either there was
a brand new tire this morning. Let's
make sure your are all. Shaky on
what we've said over. When I nor.
Any man in times past you do a lot of
you are this country you call me all of
a. Thanks for the lift buddy. Say
I'm awfully sorry about all this
you're sorry how about us we can stay
here all night you won't have to I said I
guess you're going to know all about well
how to play on the roof again how we
passed a garage about two miles back
and you take it easy Don't worry about
a thing I'll be back in a flash with
a toker watch as simple as fall off
a log. Come to. Go Go away now.
Just
a minute as one put them. Dangerous
job on. Thank you was awfully sweet
of you to stop but I'm going to
get my back turned How can you manage
the bags in front thinks my. Mind
if I sit on your lap
a little bit my dear little you are
doing convenience you but we had
a blast. This is counter to the well
what are you fighting over with it.
Would you mind getting me where you ladies
are taking me to the county in the state
oh is there anything wrong with
the gang life of the one then
a mile livin and the Ohana now.
My NY cosmos date he's usually home
guy not. Nice kid he's nice and
they remind me to send his coat that doesn't
keep me warm at all this is tough to
hear you haven't got
a lung full of the other make nice change
how it usually cold in the winter and
long in summer isn't it because no no the.
I love someone waving to us it's
a lady it's worse than that
boss is meant to stop us.
Getting. The kind of car nobody
and one of them the sitting on.
Welcome here is Are you sure this is
the kind of what they call it cheers
a life with. Thanks to this Mrs
Tom but don't wish to tie up with us
back then I waste no time around it is.
A long time but you and thanks very much
we got to be getting home with your do
divide. By.
The night Good evening likely not before
you come out. I'm the booklet with code
one of my scan I didn't see it I
didn't want to police there then.
Getting to Yes I'm really in the house
keeper How do you do this is my friend which
is. Your father's we can make things.
Would you mind reading. This weekly.
One moment please. His character if
this is just to get your father's
position. How do you do Dr Jim I like
a few words with you Miss Carrington before
you see your father. Could. Be as brief
as possible your father is far from being
a well man is getting to yes or no seeing
you for the first time may be something
of
a shock to him. I think I understand he's
been looking forward to your arrival with
great eagerness. I hope to never be any
occasion for you to be separated from him
again. Come with me please.
With.
Just
a character. This is getting to. This
is your daughter.
I. Don't know quite what to do or say. Or
why. Except to tell you.
And you're beautiful.
As the image of
a mother because she was
young. I was going to set out
yes. I. I know you
missed
a good very strange. Seeing your own father
for the first time. On the eve of your
twenty first best. Post Naturally I wondered
why you never sent for me. Your mother
love the Far East and her last wish was
to be brought up in the land she loved so
well. I wanted to send for you many times
but I had to respect your mother's wishes
. And of course my own health
wouldn't permit me to visit you and.
I hope you had a pleasant trip yes
we we had a wonderful. Way to have
a friendly one with an American girl to
which it's part of the head of an expert
and have
a Jag Richards to say.
Why. I hope you don't
mind my bringing of God. Besides
the House grounds you now know
to us now my mother tells your mothers
well everything belongs to you after to
morrow what to do around here
beside one Clark. Been here
long twenty years twenty
years that's like my to have
a steady job I'm. Your mother
wanted you to have his
hand the exact year she wore
them twenty years ago. Oh yeah.
They're Look everybody beautiful when you
as they did upon your mother. I never did
know just how
a mother died some sort of
an accident was. A mine
cave in. I met your mother in
Singapore. After you were born we
decided to move to Sumatra. But I had an
interest in toast and my. My partner was
a man named what I hope.
One day he was showing
a mother through the mine and. Suddenly
there was an earthquake in. The tunnel
collapsed you've talked enough Mr Carrington
I'm sorry to interrupt but we mustn't
. Of course now. I hope you
like your room dear I'm sure I
will show you
a tears. I'm supposed to conserve Mr
Frank quite on that good night I mean
this in the morning. Good night
after Joe night Miss Carrington.
Was voted yes.
I am. I. Then.
Oh how I know I'm all right. Well not
have happened well I don't know if it
was rather
a close call Close to six more inches would
all be singing and he doesn't live here
anymore how conjuring up
a very nice Mr Carrington you must excite
yourself. I think you'd better show the
young ladies to their rooms yet because
a couple without chandeliers
with you this weekly.
Look at the Chinese Room will
be yours Mr Richards you know.
When this is just dandy I travel seven
thousand miles to get away from Chinaman and
here I am with everything but
a bowl of rice. But that sounds like the
waves angry waves day to day the night
after night they beat with savage beauty
going to Black Rock built for twenty years
to be calling calling calling to someone
who never danced and just like
a pot of gold program. So that the young
is no I'm starved You forgot we didn't
have the dinner round I will
bring you a tray Oh and
a little thing I'll do not just that and
be able nothing heavy anything for you
Miss Carrington's knows I'm here only I'm
going to bed Gail all in and kind of
begging myself. To take me sick just good
night I hope you rest in peace thank you
. But they went on to Stones Don't
be silly go on to bed about.
Your father had to shoot done especially
for you lovely story Miss but we have no
beer I brought you some wine
wine. Yes me put together
a body will be anything else come
back all thank you. Champney. I
hide it. But just.
To let you know this me
little bit of money and.
She. Wears
a glass slipper the good with it is nice
isn't it nice that you have been compared
to that Chinese torture chamber on T.V.
Layoffs. Oh. I've always
wanted to live in one
of these covered wagons. Almost to night
to sleep in and think What do you have to
do to get
a bed like this rubber magic lamp. You
really like to jam just. Right up my
alley own a kitchen
measles have to stay in
a bed like you. Say
where you don't go into bed for night
darling this room enjoyed Oh no you don't I
wouldn't dream of letting you do anything
like that but it's to do you anything to
keep out of China Good night Cinderella
good night hell and I do the. Lock your
door and take Lady
Frankenstein walk in or sleep.
Did you wish anything doctor the young
lady is comfortable once. That.
I don't mind if you.
I know what I'd like.
For.
World.
Where you're all the
low wall to wall the whole.
Wall. Old.
Girl all right old.
Woman.
Old.
Saw I. Met an
epitome. Of.
You know all right schoolboys I. Told you
repeatedly and incest when I could get
a word in edgewise but the whole thing was
no fault of mine I think it's ridiculous
for
a man of your age to pursue Young goes through
the neighborhoods think I didn't care
or they forced themselves to go beyond
said imagine goes pretty good pushing
themselves on
a paunchy middle aged man why I don't think
I'm point you don't try to change the
subject to my do you mean when you went
on to explain that darling I couldn't get
a girl was sitting on my lap I know she
was I won your cousin know if ever you
would do anything like this again. Back
to. Town of course I don't intend to do
a thing like that again sighed I know I
couldn't videos have. Caused this is
hard it can joke. Speak you'll hear
I don't think it took you after all we've
been married for twenty years and I have
nothing to be treated like
a wife who who has been married for
twenty years that's odd. Do you
realize what you're saying. I make
a bundle that's all the attention you're
going to give me I may as well go to bed
at night. I might be
a little overweight but I'm certainly not
punching. In fact I'm in pretty good
shape for the shape I'm in
a former banker and the grammar boy. Get
your cold feet off my back. You
don't need all the covers do you.
Remember me the girl looked out on your
lap Oh this is terrible but terrible year
ago Stuart did knock it because you gotta
get out of here I don't have trouble of
your kind of people change I should be
dead I was young and healthy my thoughts
well what I wanted they had so why did I
die I don't know what you can say here you
want to go back to the getting to the
house can't. You see him go do something
vanish Well all right happy
here at all. Or if you're here
cause no one knows who you are talking to
nobody and nobody I was just talking in
my sleep you're talking in your sleep but
that's it you waste of time in the sack
nobody can hear you oh I'm not so sure
about that cause more I am sorry I was so
mean I know you tell me if there was
anything between you and that gal that let's
forget all about him I'd like to hear about
under the circumstances I'm afraid I
can't know what of course that the way
you feel about it I talk to you in the
morning when you're sober.
Why don't you look where you're going why
don't you be where you are now see what
you've done that's nothing compared to what
I'm going to do if you don't come with
me come with you where back to the character
Now I'm curious to know what happened
to me Go away oh no no I couldn't go alone
I'm afraid I don't like that house it's
kooky I won't go that's the way you
feel about it get up to my bed I bought
let you come with me you get out of my
better I'm going to drop what you tell until
you're in my bed. Oh I like Over want of
a not very well but I can't open you
wouldn't do that the doctor wouldn't
understand you coming with me or not I
come home all right again I'll give you
three to make up your mind and then
I'll scream Oh well you know you don't
oh if you when oh when you want me don't
call yourself or intend to take us to the
can't.
All. Yes what. Are
you. All you know that oh yeah right oh
well.
What are you getting at. I wish
our little. Well come on get
going. Yesterday.
Where I don't have to dominate Cannington
face my main part but last saw to inquire
what was going to carry the place
belong. To look for a body. That
a loved one from
a joke of the one I'm
using now is now. Come
on if you want to help me you know
what boss with about it the but.
OK I'll go with you but kind of
keep to one side because I've got
a feeling some rat is going they don't.
Attack me that's the big rumor machine the
moment that could be How we going
to get in through the window.
I'm a bust but could I
get confidential for
a moment what does it. Look as pale
as I feel for matter with you.
I don't know but there's
somebody here I can account for
a come on come up. For. Me around having.
Them
a rabbit trying. Copies
of Windows Let's see if we can get him we
can do that to wake up the house so don't
argue here and if you just want to.
Ready here. For diet.
Try the window.
And give me. Where are you thank you.
Is the will and.
Where Well you will let me see oh
yes I was sleeping in that scene
and it seems I got up to close the window
there was that window of the and I
started back to bed in and that's all I
remember oh my gosh the man look right by
the window.
Positively horrible you been stamped dad.
This is no time to champion
overtopping It isn't every day
a girl gets murdered. Oh. Please
please be because you seriously but to
call the police yes I want to find on did
this to me where the phone down stated.
And no. Operator. Operator operator.
Thing did an epidemic where I am
sweetie. Coughing to get anybody
maybe the wires and cut
all trace the. Operator.
Operator. Could.
Stay where you are. You
know phones out of all
who are you know me. I'm
Cosmo Tapa I'm next on
a. Nice thank you.
And I just dropped in the phone at twelve
thirty in the morning with either any one
to. Be going. Through your calling
the police there's been
a murder here. And
don't look at me like that I I didn't kill
the girl what on earth are you people
doing and I found this man crying about the
house this gentleman has been thinking
what are you talking about if you don't
believe me go and see if yourself or
Jeanette big room at the top of
the stairs. Why trans room go on.
Right over there by the window. Well
there's no one here.
I saw idea
a few minutes ago in my own I guess.
Father what's the matter. How to
be your safe your mind because I am why I
was getting to this when I was just being
to the US that you would be mowed Ole Miss
to talk to whatever gave you that idea
no we cannot DO YOU WANT
TO THE OTHER go I saw in
a moment ago now really I did where is
Caylee she wasn't downstairs with her of
course not how would you be downstairs
when she was murdered up here to top up
please control yourself. I think I found
something that might explain that
is it's
a bitch to miss getting to. Dolly Sorry
to run out on you so mysterious they will
explain everything when I get back love
Gail used to talk it over the suffering
from a lucid notion of the top
a. Hold of you forty six.
Just as I thought what do you mean just to
do thought schizophrenia ski differently
I'm nothing I came here in my car oh.
Yeah it is it's right outside no
waiting for me.
It's like yes ma'am I know what is wrong
with you and they may use them planes
thing always clone bottom circles people
talk with enough and get no answers I'm
going back to Mr Barry enough like this
never happened I almost double his status
as Mr Kaplan he's almost like and in place
I go again I mean I want to find out why
tell us
a joke and they get on your clothes we're
going right over there shoot me and I am
but I am in the war was standing up you
know going to guide us but. That's what I
was afraid of normal as normal as you'd
expect for this type of man I've lost the
body and lost my car if I don't get out
of here very soon I'll lose my mind you
know what he needs more than
a thing else is risking when he feels
better going to send him home in my car and
you better go to bed good night Mr Top
good night. This is tough it kills
a parent has me worried well look what
he's done to me where did you last see her
she was sitting on
a table in the hole in Gee hung my head
on the Chinaman's foot. Just take it easy
Mr topper and curl the long few minutes.
Remember they just what are you doing
here but I hate to be commercially but
somebody owes me twenty six eighty that's
right. I'm sorry I forgot also forgot to
say goodbye the queue disappearing at you
when your partner called you by chance
see you didn't pass around the red love
what is she sleepwalker I don't know that
she's gone or disappeared
again say she was the right
a magician. I got you money for
a. What's
the matter. Anything wrong.
I had to go up the stairs.
Would you mind coming with me.
I stand. With you.
I'm gonna come back in the
morning I want you. To name
a jam or something. Just never
seem to get this why. I can
explain. Things been happening
a while you can stop worrying honey nothing's
going to happen to you Come on. Take
the private life Bill
a joint like this oh this is my room well
if you don't mind I'll just wait here.
And. What's going on here was I kind of
like hope when I don't know her well you
know I just could not find
a way to keep our women screaming boogie
men jumping out of windows but I was like
this I would want to keep it going getting
to. Getting. What's going on here and
I just said that who are you and don't
tell me you're this girl's rich uncle I
don't usually I'm the father that's close
enough I'm thinking I'll bet you the
first thing she says when she opens
arises where am I. Plugged in and.
Say what are you doing here all right so
long to explain it to you this young lady
owes me for
a taxi cab ride I came here to collect
it she asked me up to this room I heard
a scream and walked into the middle of
an Orson Welles broadcast and then was
standing over me with
a knife against it what did you do about
knife I found another window in the next
room talking just what he was right he
said they murdered the other girl. Now
they're trying to move on Rama
call the police. Oh and I wait
a minute you don't think I had anything
to do with this. What to you I said well
enough and you had better go toes on.
I'm afraid you're going to remain here.
But good heavens why didn't he want to kill
Miss Carrington only kill me didn't say
if I can understand that but Miss can I
don't worry about her any more she's got
a knife can somebody guide he's
a taxi driver maybe he's the one doing all
the killing nonsense he didn't bring his
camp with him. Well and she's safe and
the reason we just say good night I had
a lovely photo op you don't run out now
well you've got to find out who killed me
then we'll know who's threatening and I am
but I don't want my wife threatening me
as he and she will if you
find out no I'm going home.
I'm quite sure you're mistaken fine I say
can I not I knew that you had like yes
ma'am but I don't think that was the
general with me I said I don't know what I
mean I don't frankly Madame I don't know
what the bill does why do you say we start
from the beginning that's
a good idea but that is my husband
but I don't know what this is
a private home private much more like
a fine Crown can I help you you
certainly can. Do you want to hear.
Yes I do I'm at the top I'm looking for
my husband Mr TUCKER Oh Where does the of
yours the one that goes around sitting
on people's well as has been murdered
according to your husband don't change the
subject if you won't help us we'll find
him also to come along and I think you'll
find him in the sitting room the sitting
room maybe she still sitting on his lap
sitting on the ledge Good heavens you mean
you've got
a room just for that purpose right
this way come on in because. She
comes you've got to go I don't trust you
Bunny you tried to run out of me how can I
run out with her there and how can I face
her with you hear sounds logical OK here
we go. Fellas.
So. Why not. He was here
a few minutes ago Rama what happened to
him I don't know said but I'm positive he
hasn't left the house and he will not
feel I find him and given that he's in my
mind do you mind not at all spread the
telephone right this way so that I'm going
to be. Caught.
Up when I got operated on I want to report
a missing husband said Well if you look
what I've done that's what I. Saw bulldog
down there darkness never heard anyone say
that the darkness will stop it is what
we haven't don't be silly there's no
difference between light and dark except the
lights are out. I'll go over
every AM I go to stand on
him. As well Tapper.
What's he look like next
a banker of course that's because he is
a banker. Well can you describe him well
he wears a size sixteen should with
a thirty three sleeve a nine and
a half sock. And it's likely both Oh yes
and something else let me see I paid the
milkman and that one's
been changing so it's
a different ID Oh yes it is good
I'm good. Yes murder capital
and you. Are wrong the idea. Kind to make
these policeman understand something is
harder than doing it just.
Because the top. They added
a cigarette. Could
be
a match. And
it.
Would stop. But. It's
a cop out. Oh
I.
Oh.
Well. The
you. Like.
What are you doing here oh
where are you really getting
a. Little. JOHN MEYER to tell you the knock
on the ladies bit to go before your bog
This is most embarrassing I
couldn't do stay the way you were
a negligent Toddy probably
at the top inclined. To.
Come on top you've got things to do.
To get out of here. Kind.
I'm headquarters was
a pub where the rubble say no don't stand
there dumb I got a phone call about
a half an hour ago there's been
a minor and maybe you'll
get it. In here quick.
This must be because it was not
amusing. He's not here how.
Can he be.
Good no. It's just he in
here. You pick up the cake
and he makes him keep. His to go
with. I must have time for him
and you know we never
drink tea Yes I know.
I met. One of them did you see the face
of the man of all the Coke you know it it
was covered up somebody is covering up
a lot of things around here why don't you
let her alone she's nervous and upset she
hears how do you think I feel I'm under
no body didn't anybody see your body and
you said topper said he saw the body I
double talk to stop these men say they saw
the body when I say he's gone he's gone.
The body's gone so why are you people
trying to do to me I'm sure Sergeant
it's nothing but a tempest in
a teapot Miscavige and heaven knows when
the supposedly dead girl that will clearly
be all up where's I know it's gone the
most. Profitable nobody's gone now look
here I don't have to come here to be made
a hole are. A. Big part I'm saying
but I believe Miss Cardigan left and up
there you took the boys up stairs searching
everywhere don't there's anything tearing
apart. Oh look here Rebecca what stalling
Where is this guy topper I don't know
what was he doing here the first place I
don't know so you want to go to my car am
I don't know who's this first guy oh he's
all right in the taxi driver Yeah well
where's your taxi Now don't tell me that's
disappeared too what do you think it is I'm
not supposed to think I'm from the city
hall now where was I I
don't know but. Emmett is
K.Q.
Simply didn't read you like it is the best
you've ever made this is not arcane I've
got some cream in me
please train this back.
Oh I wish. I.
Could only. I don't want to do you doing.
Something And you know it's chilly out so
but you don't know that you just did you
know I spoke getting out of
a nice one day to come and sit in someone's
ice box I don't understand you but I do
understand it don't I and I hope
so. That's Green came from here
a lot of problems for you I mean you've
got who are you Mrs topper. Well you
know has been in the arts back as you
get about thirty and you can work out.
So your talk. With your mind coming out
of cold storage I will not say what's the
matter with him is the icebox crazy
you're suffering from hell is
a nation Oh you wouldn't buy a
Chesapeake thinking you were
a lamb chop now what you mean by stealing
this house in the middle of the night
what if you don't know that
you had on your neck on
a slab or Oh I love triangle Do you really
think all of this is I get it you sneak
in here to see some gal your wife thought
you had to get rid of the day before you
knocked off yes or no I did not wear
somebody I don't know so you admit there is
a body and I came over here to look for it
but how do you know what she told me she
who see the dead go away get
worried I'm going to push and
talk I don't know but this one does oh I
mean I know you won't believe what I'm
going to tell you but where we where
were you when the attack was made
a miscarriage is life. And the library I
think I don't know did you want to do not
try to save this young lady I don't think
we did you know delve into cars in the
woods did anybody got even God
a dirty. Now listen lady somebody kills
the name of the talks after she's dead
and the body gets up and walks away somebody
tried to wiggle on this young lady and
I find them hiding the I didn't. Want to
just place you when you're going to have
all these in exactly Charmbracelet
slating. He's going to come.
It's mine in the end that he's got.
Somebody. You want the fix
but that's it if I go out.
Do that they'll.
Go out on me go of me. You should've made
me do that you want to go to jail no
but we can go on like this my wife the
police what do you suppose they think they
think you're guilty of housebreaking and
murder come on and find my body well
because after we do find it and I will
be accused of murdering that evidence to
prove you're innocent why David just know
I was supposed to written and to take
footage I'll tell you
when we find me come up.
My goodness what they felt caught in here.
Bless you you were in your husband when
it comes up you know how good
a time for you is so you take the cake
I only get the small piece of anything
that's no reason we should be locked
up in a mishap complaining but I'm
a personal man in mathematics only I think
Shut up will or can't do more harm come
to break down my door test fires
all right. Funny noise that's my
truth trash right what is your problem
in your pocket oh I just proved our need
a screwdriver to get me out. All on my
guess that all my Come on everybody we're
going to have the right to be something
we can use. Other stuff we're going to
start processing time maybe just shake
up something with like you may I suggest
spirit you write the bus are great the bus
OK. Well good luck to you he means the
glass in the door dummy
OK but I think it'll have
a little bit. Oh
wait
a minute I'll take charge of this you take
me up stairs and you take that out of
state take this personally I think that you
call the police well I'll take care of
that ticket for fingerprints.
The way. You.
Might be.
OK Where you been last Exxon Valdez even
though you still in full body if it
was down but it just live. Aid
left it just put out to sea that's
a true boss but I'm going back to
prove it oh yes you are. Yes but
our lack of things I get myself into
a month. And
a young going to stay right here until
we can say. Yes. But don't there
are legit up or down.
The path. Come your characters on
the phone get up front let me get around.
Here we go all girl. Group.
Yes it is. A field while I love. Her You
don't yell give me your hand why no one
I've ever seen honors I got from the bottom
M.C.R. Some pants on you and
I don't want to see and
a guy ask questions now I say we
don't. Right here right now we've got
a live shot ten miles of kind
of the oh why not wrap up in
a concrete my back and drop my right here
that tired I'll take out extra blossoms
orders and don't argue with me go
below and get that interest up OK.
Again coming in like.
You are in here. On the
D.L.
And it's too uncomfortable. Duffy
And we've got to get off now you
know what about particular them.
Want.
It Back in general I have
a staff. I don't know. You
tell me how I expected in
general to just kind of. Get it
but you have
a way. And
leave it on.
I didn't do what I missed I got.
For.
You if you'd asked me that
a second later you'd have
been talking to yourself. So
the body. Don't. Know I'm
bringing it back bring it.
Brother you got
a lot of questions that. You know.
Don't talk about. Everybody
here. Get this straight.
Nobody says from unless I say so. And
you stop showing that girl just.
Not you. I'm sorry Miss Carrington
I know this is going to be
a bit of pleasant for you but would you
mind stepping in the next room with me.
This can I can. I'm going to raise this
you. See if you can identify this young
lady.
Hello she's been living here she came
here tonight to Miss Carrington.
Too bad she had to go so you know.
She's got awful big think tell.
Me when I was in looks. With you when I
dream just now. That now they're all an
hour well don't tell me the joints heart
Now look I was standin in that room
minded my own business just as I say
what big Fiji's got I get slapped in the
kisser. Who did that.
I went out that door nobody now wait
a minute dollars just open and shut
themselves but that one did. Hey want to cut
off your booty will you feel better dear
boy she be all right of Charlie Chan
a letter alone thousand Ravitch I don't
like to interfere but is it necessary to
subject my daughter to all this she's
telling me now this would you would you
please let her go to her room Nobody leaves
this room not even me and that goes for
the both of you.
Think the match mine will give anything.
Everything. You don't mind
of. Innocent men stay home
nights they don't hide and iceboxes and I
don't take dead bodies on both rides Why
did you kill or I didn't that's only
one man's opinion I can prove it
out. Leave me alone in that room for
a minute of all I'm not that down let's
only one man's opinion to others
to let him have his way there are no windows
in the trophy room and the Ice Box is
no All right I'll give you three minutes
if you're not back in this room with
a fourteen carat alibi this lady is going
to make one of the most charming widows
I've ever met tell her
yank you up this year.
OK Gale Well you.
Know the battle for the right
when you. Have the thing.
Good all right. Stand up and behave
yourself to it I mean last year. Stop it
when you stop when there is no time to be
faithful. There's no. One you
know. The proof you said you
had. I want to lie down and.
You can get sleepy now you
got me into this you got
to get me out of it and.
He moved from he tried to
walk straight. Through the
couch there. For
good. Coffee.
If yes when he said no I'm not. Trying to
be what you get we don't want to be in
this. Town to. Try to think.
I don't please. Try to pull
yourself together when you. Little.
A lot.
They got
a little headache and you
got an aspirin and you. No.
But I'll get you. That
settles that guy says nothing
is a candy bar set for
a straight jacket like I took one for me.
Now where I know.
What does this prove I didn't
write it or did I have. The same
handwriting. And identical.
Then she must be you know if.
You like but you wrote that
letter don't you. Yes this is
a note you found in the well
a girl's room. Then how do you account
for the both doing the same harrowing. I
don't know listen sister it
looks like you're all set for
a first degree murder rap. Because
to become cleanly could go
a little easier I know I wasn't alone in
this I don't know but I didn't kill or who
did.
And I'm going to. Find another
right. There's
a pickpocket if you like what I stole
and what does put our back such as well
especially our spots like the attic where
the attic thanks me I've been in politics
ten years and I've never seen
anything pulled up and it's.
Got the front door don't let anybody you
know what's down there that's my kitchen
if I find that dame in the icebox are
resigned and I'll drop their. Cup come brace
up brace up I'd appreciate it so much if
you stay here with my daughter I want to
talk to such a girl that I will be
a pleasure. I
think. I do you know we invented
a if you don't know how far you go on
I don't know why I. Don't know that I
disagree but I think.
So I'm going to get. State here.
Sounds like my wife.
Is going to. This gang. Is
getting to. Be scanning just.
Where she was here
a second ago Watch happens not just can you
disappear when I left it was him saying
What is this the fun house of the page
everybody the talks you just appears now I'm
talking to you I suppose I'm turning up
missing that is the best suggestion you've
made tonight well that's all
right don't you little park near
a fire plug after you I I want to go
home I'll tell you one don't call
and I'll tell you what
up though. Chain around.
The cable and has disappeared disappear
entirely but we've got to find me out of
this site well they can't stop me.
You'll go out there and you talk to
just outside kickstand.
Where when you hear what we were
where. You were I mean that that is
good there wasn't any no yes there was
I love you both in that room pardon me
Mistah was getting Kylie always said was
it all any good don't you that yes we can
do I think after twenty years of married
life you wouldn't try to deceive me I
remember our honeymoon in Atlantic City
about me you never know who's going to.
Let people like you do you
know you'll be able to go.
Yes I'm not.
A. Techie.
Canopies I had
a frightful night was when I was in Manchuria
whatever you do don't send that shit
anybody really stop interrupting you at
all he's running out of like you have an
odd Condie they need him but he hasn't told
me and now you know I can't stand much
more all of us that shares receptive
destructible distrust worry and this is the
voice of experience what are you talking
about well if you sit in that chair and
things happen quite Oh don't talk nonsense
says it's serious look Bush I sat in
that shit just like this but my legs
just like this lame back here I go on
and. I get to see what you need to
room I didn't do you even know there's
a time. For the saying I always
stand by you no matter what
happens they're just people hide will be
well exactly what you feel about it I
won't say another word.
You know what I mean you know nothing idea
we should have one of these you know how
this whole weekend it's. Going to
hit me so you get out of there.
OK you take Adama's when you go up stairs
you're going to find me going I'll be
right here or I want to night I remember
going to try to remember to go on about.
Oh I sure needed that one copy I just saw
the manager in the cellar Who is he I
don't know I can see his face
and he was all muffled up in
a big black cloak Well whoever he is he
was in that room when the housekeeper
disappeared because I found the contraption
the fabric lover of the chair she was
sitting on top floor we've got to make
a convict him self Oh you said in that
chair and tell them that you know who the
murdering is me so you know. But others
appear to own or not if you keep your eye
on the fireplace and the
first one that makes
a move toward that someone
more after. You know afraid.
What makes you think I don't know and I
simply want to tell all I know virtually
really long so now now kind
of a stalling and go get
a rigid to put them out. The first
bait the one they wanted to kill was Miss
Carrington Well never mind who they were
after. The murderer. Didn't
know he'd kill the wrong when he found out
he was panicking and hid the body you
see Dr I did not have
a losing nation very interesting. So
when he watches the fireplace for
what he expects Santa Claus come
a whole time. The housekeeper knew
he knew too much she wasn't the one.
When she was about to confess. She
disappeared from this very chair.
And the person who called her disappearance
was standing right beside this
Firebrace when it happened what you're
saying is looking right strategy to
a man's man and I was nowhere near the
fireplace when it happened I was over there
. Rama you were standing by
the fireplace you're mistaken
Dr Jared I was standing by
the library door oh wait
a minute who was standing by the fireplace
when the housekeeper disappeared. Father
you. Come to think of it I was Mr
Carrington would you mind sitting
in that chair. Of course not.
And I'm not going to. Have.
My mother never mind that put your
hands up cold and if you got in
a sense you want to Hamas and you say
that's how it was meant. Charge and
dramatist been a pleasure
to do business with
a man of the audit intelligence. That
.
Are now.
Take your hand on that.
We. Don't mean that the
time down.
To us. That magic
coming.
To.
US
cuckoo
Q Q
two posts.
To it.
Left.
Man it serves you right Oh I'd hate to be
in your shoes first murder now reckless
driving
a recording angel certainly throw the
book at you soon what are you doing here
studio by
a BIG Now why did you try to kill your
daughter Oh don't be silly I'm not I'm
a father who are you a hobbit Carrington's
partner Carrington was killed in
a mine cave in so that's why you ghost of
a double crossed in crook and must know
about this too late no no we're stuck here
to find out and when she knows the truth I
can go to heaven and you can go to give
me a pencil quick and a piece of
paper when I'm going to. Take
a letter. Dear And I am
not to bother period.
Then as he was looking for an actor to be
sure of how that this is going to cost
him his private life that you know
that it. Did happen give this guy.
I'm sorry about your
father was going to wait
a minute he wasn't up father
was going to this is.
What WATCH is all about but here it is or
am I expecting too much. But if you could
just know it. Through into my. Notes
the flying father said they'd
follow your chair Come on let's get out
of here before the tree start talking.
To you. And here I go and I come back
here not me from now on I used to be your
shoulder if you want to drive us home not
in that car enough is enough and that's
what I have an abundance of very well
that's the way you feel about it and it
will drive. And God I know this guy and I
are shit on you and I don't think.
Any you know I did you know ma'am.
Thank you Eve been a great help. Sorry
I had to dunk you in the water oh boy.